HANS PHILIPP NEISSER PAPERS (GER069) 1918-1971
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Reprints & Book reviews, Undated; 2
  - Book Reviews, Undated; 2.2
    - 16)Gold and Monetary Stabilization, Letures, on the Harris Foundation 1932. From: Weltwirstchaftlichens Archiv. 37. Band /Heft. 1, Januar 1933
      by Jacob Viner, Prof. of Economics, University of Chicago, Gottfried Haberler, Privatdozent, University of Vienna, H. Parker Willis, Prof. of Banking, Columbia Univ., Lionel D. Edie, John H. Williams, Prof. of Economics, Harvard University of Chicago 1932. The University of Chicago Press, XI, 1738. Reviewed by: Privatdozent Dr. Hans Neisser, Kiel.
    - 17) Lö sch, August.The Economics of Location. New Haven: Yale University Press. 1954. XXVIII & 520 pp. reviewed by H. Neisser From: Social Research, 1956 Spring
    - 18) "Deutschland und Frankreich". Thee Wirtschaft und ihre Politik 1923/24. Herausgegeben von R. Kuczynski. Berlin 1924, bei R.L. Prager. 411. Reviewed by H. Neisser, from:Die Gesellschaft - Internationale Revue Für Sozialismus und Politik Nummer 8.I. Jahrgang, 1924 November
    - 19) Baster, A. S. J.The Imperial Banks. London 1929 P.S. King and San, reviewed by Hans Neisser, source-unknown, Undated
    - 20) Geschichte der Wissenschaft. Encyklopädisches, Lehrbücher. Spezielle Theoretische Untersuchungen. Helander, Sven, Die Ausgangspunkte der Wirtschaftswissenschaft. Jena (Gustav Fischer) 1923 8. 122SS. Reviewed by Hans Neisser from: Uebersicht uber die neuesten Publikationen Deutschlands und des Auslandes, Undated
    - 21) Santos, Clemer: Kooperation der Not enbanklen als Mittel zur Rationalisierung der Wirtwirtschaft. Tubingen 1931 Verlag von J. C. B. Mohr (Baul V) and 116S, Undated
    - 21) Schleivt, Alexander: Die Kooperation der Not enbanken. Ball 1931, Werlag (S)elbeng Sonderabzug & Licontewhan- VIII und 176s, Undated; reprint
      Reviewed by Hans Neisser, from: Sonderabzug aus S(ch)mollers Fahrber(05) Für Gesetzgebung, Verwaltung und Volkswirtschaft im Deuts(05) Jahrgang 56 Heft II 1932
    - 22) A Supplementary Note to the Article: "The Static Theory of Aggregate Investment" by Hans Neisser, 1967
      Reprinted from: Weltwirschaftliches Archiv Band 99 Heft 1
    - 23) Hans Neisser On the Sociology of Knowledge, an Essay. Copyright - 1965, James H. Heineman, Inc., New York, N. Y., Undated